Now let me just point out one thing quickly before we go on to how we can concede a point and that is
现在让我快速指出一件事，然后再继续我们如何承认一分，那就是
the power of analogies and basically how we do that.
类比的力量以及我们如何做到这一点。
I'm going to just give you a quick example and an explanation for what an analogy is basically an analogy
我将给你一个简单的例子，并解释什么是类比基本上是类比
is a simplified example that helps people understand a more complex thing.
是一个简化的例子，可以帮助人们理解更复杂的事情。
So if we're having a debate or a discussion about politics around the world or whatever and we're talking
因此，如果我们正在就世界各地的政治或其他任何事情进行辩论或讨论，而我们正在谈论
about the United States and Canada let's say let's say we're talking about the United States and Canada.
关于美国和加拿大 假设我们正在谈论美国和加拿大。
Well things when we're talking about countries can be very complicated really complicated.
好吧，当我们谈论国家时，事情可能非常复杂非常复杂。
So we might make an analogy or a simplified example as a way to help people understand the picture.
所以我们可以做一个类比或简化的例子来帮助人们理解图片。
I don't want to set up the whole debate here.
我不想在这里展开整个辩论。
I don't even want to make a real point.
我什至不想提出真正的观点。
I just want to show you what an analogy is and how you could make one and they can be used everywhere
我只是想向您展示什么是类比以及如何制作类比，并且它们可以在任何地方使用
in a debate because if you make things too complex too complicated then people who are listening to
在辩论中，因为如果你让事情变得太复杂太复杂，那么正在倾听的人
the debate might become confused the audience.
辩论可能会使听众感到困惑。
If there is an audience will wonder what you're talking about because you can't explain your ideas simply.
如果有观众会想知道你在说什么，因为你不能简单地解释你的想法。
So that's why analogies or simplified examples can help.
所以这就是类比或简化示例可以提供帮助的原因。
That's really what an analogy is a simplified example.
这真的是一个类比是一个简化的例子。
So making examples is a powerful tool in helping the other people who are listening understand what
因此，制作示例是帮助其他正在倾听的人理解内容的有力工具
you mean.
你的意思是。
So here's an analogy.
所以这里有一个类比。
And this is how we can begin an analogy one way we can do this is to say Here's an analogy imagine there
这就是我们如何开始一个类比我们可以这样做的一种方法是说这是一个类比想象那里
are two brothers.
是两个兄弟。
One is big and confident and everyone knows about him.
一个大而自信，每个人都知道他。
The other is more laid back and easier to get along with.
另一个更悠闲，更容易相处。
This is the relationship between Canada and the United States or this is the situation with Canada and
这是加拿大和美国之间的关系，或者这是加拿大和美国的情况
the United States.
美国。
Now I'm not sure if that's a great analogy.
现在我不确定这是否是一个很好的类比。
I don't really care about world politics that much but I'm just trying to say the view that people have
我不太关心世界政治，但我只是想说人们的看法
of countries and politics with countries that's very complicated.
国家和政治与非常复杂的国家。
But the idea of two brothers to help people understand something that's a lot simpler and people can
但是两个兄弟帮助人们理解的想法要简单得多，人们可以
understand the relationship between two brothers.
了解两兄弟之间的关系。
People can understand the characteristics of a person or two people side by side.
人们可以并排了解一个人或两个人的特征。
OK so I've used that simpler example to help you get an idea of the larger and more complicated point
好的，所以我使用了那个更简单的例子来帮助你了解更大更复杂的观点
I'm trying to make.
我正在尝试制作。
When you can use analogies if you can't make an analogy that's OK explain your point in more detail
什么时候可以使用类比 如果你不能做一个可以的类比 更详细地解释你的观点
but could be a very useful way to get the audience on your side and to get them to understand you more
但可能是一种非常有用的方式，可以让观众站在你这边，让他们更了解你
easily than maybe the other side.
比对方容易。